# CHANODOM UTSAHAJIT

# **CONTACT INFORMATION**

079-569-82635 | 074-551-45159

BZKWORK1993@GMAIL.COM

CHANODOM-UTSAHAJIT.COM

FLAT 1 ARGYLE HOUSE 1 DEE ROAD RICHMOND, UK TW9 2JN

# **SKILLSET**

UX / UI DESIGN



SERVICE DESIGN





BUSINESS INNOVATION



FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT

## **TOOLKITS**

#### VISUAL DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP



**ILLUSTRATOR** 



AFTER EFFECTS



EXPERIENCE DESIGN







UNITY 3D



HTML5 + CSS3 + JS





TOBII EYE TRACKING



MORAE

# **LANGUAGES**

THAI

MOTHER-TONGUE

**ENGLISH** 

**JAPANESE** 

BEGINNER

# **INTERESTS**

VIRTUAL & AUGMENTED REALITY



GAME DEVELOPMENT



TRAVEL & EXPLORATION



**EXTREME SPORTS & TRIATHLON** 

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a recent graduate in the field of UX design, Business, and Technology with an experience and passion for designing and innovating digital experiences using state-of-the-art technology and methodologies. Additionally, my proficiency in visualisation allows me to perform creative tasks, as well as to collaborate and communicate ideas at ease through illustrations and infographics.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

VIKER (FEB 2018 - APR 2018) **UX/CREATIVE INTERN** 

Involved directly in hypercasual mobile game developments, assisting in user experience design process and graphical assets creation. Created early Unity-based prototypes, UA videos and App Store contents for published games.



KEY

Wireframing &

**LEARNINGS** 

# PRECISION PRINTING (OCT 2016 - JAN 2017)

CREATIVE INTERN

In charge of the production of graphical materials for blogs, and the visual redesign of customer artwork guideline documents for the purpose of better comprehension and modernisation.



& Typography

PwC UK (JUN 2016 - AUG 2016) CONSULTING INTERN

Acted as a visual UX designer for 'Startup Journey' project, responsible for potential customer research and analysis, and prototyping which includes UI redesign wireframing and



Research & Media Prototyping

# CYBERPRINT GROUP (JUN 2015 - AUG 2015)

CONSULTING INTERN

Assisted in the company's adoption of digital printing. Further led the planning of personalised promotional offerings and print prototyping for Mother's Day and National Book Exhibition Week.



Business Model

CHOMASOFT (JUN 2014 - JAN 2016)

CO-FOUNDER

Acted as a co-project manager for the mobile game development of 'Rubber Dash Story'. Experimented with Scrum to lead the development process. Involved in the UI and gameplay concept ideation process, and minor front-end code edits.



SAMAGGI SAMAGOM (SEP 2013 - JUL 2014) MEDIA CREATOR VOLUNTEER

Responsible for the production of advertisement materials such as posters and videos for charity and public events. Co-produced promotional video for Samaggi Concert feat. LIPTA and social media posters for Samaggi Games 2014.



Team Building & Under Pressure

# **EDUCATION**

#### **USER EXPERIENCE DESIGN (UXD)** (2017 - 2018)

KINGSTON UNIVERSITY LONDON

User Research, Customer Jouneys & Personas, Wireframing, Rapid Prototyping, Usability Testing, Desgin Thinking, Digital Studio Practice (++)

# INNOVATION, ENTREPRENEURSHIP **& MANAGEMENT (IEM)** (2015 - 2016)

IMPERIAL COLLEGE BUSINESS SCHOOL

Business Economics, Organisational Behavior & HR Management, Project & Strategic Management, Design & Innovation Management, Agile, International Marketing (++)

## **COMPUTER SCIENCE** WITH INTELLIGENT SYSTEMS (2012 - 2015)

KING'S COLLEGE LONDON

Introductory Artificial Intelligent, Introductory Robotics, Computing Foundations, Object-Oriented Programming, Computer Vision (++)



Dissertation: "Service Redesign to transform CyberPrint Group, a Printing Corporate, towards Digital



Dissertation: "How to create Innovation from within an





Dissertation: "How Visual Richness in a Virtual Reality Environment affects the Interaction Performance of Users?